Why are you...
Are you there?
Hey Gyeonwoo
Huh?
Ah, Gyeonwoo!
Save me, no matter what I do
I'll stop all the bad luck
Grandma's grandson?
I will keep you alive for three to seven days.
Did you come to the funeral?
I heard it from Jiho.
How did I get there?
I was never there
Something without a beard
Did I come to see you?
I came to see your grandmother!
Bad things seemed destined
Because I'm always ready
Good things... seemed like miracles
Because it won't happen
Until the darkness disappears and the light comes
There is a child who will protect you by your side.
His hands are so warm
I can be happy at least once
I had a vain dream...
Hey Gyeonwoo
Gyeonwoo Bae!
Gyeonwoo...
I'm sorry, Gyeonwoo.
don't cry
I cry because I did a good job
Nice to meet you?
Should I do it?
Did you turn?
Do it tomorrow, do it tomorrow
Not today
Is this crazy, Mr.
Ugh, sir!
uh?
what?
I...
What did you do so wrong?
Who says not to hate?
I told you to hate me
Even if I hate you to death, I can't do anything
You know it!
Just...
I just hate you
Just hate
Why are you doing this to me, why!
I...
How much more pitiful must I be...
Are you going to quit?
Hey Gyeonwoo
I'm sorry
Mr...
Go!
Go away!
please!
I didn't say it to you when I told you to go.
A shaman, really.
It's shameless
It must have been fun, so far
It's not like that
I meant to say it from the beginning
But because you hate it so much
Now I feel sorry for myself
It's going to be fun soon, right?
I heard bad luck, I got evil
It's not long before I die
Making fun of me with all kinds of words
It's going to be fun
Watching me struggle
It's not like someone hung it on a rope.
Doing everything I'm told like a puppet
You'll laugh at that too
I'm trying so hard
Soaked in boiling water
I didn't even know it was a frog
I am different from other shamans
The things I say now
This may all sound like excuses, but...
It's not an excuse
It's a lie
Of all the things you've said to me so far
How many things are not lies?
who is this?
Who could be so vicious!
To make the guy inside an evil spirit
It's a deliberate barrier
Equivalent exchange
I risked my life over there
Seal the inside from the outside
Not even a single ant can enter.
If you can't go inside the house
There is no need to become a sacrifice!
Close the door and camp out
Sunrise Dongbang.
Ochikchabu Boje Buddha Statue
Close the door and camp out
One day and one day samadhi
If you are Bokbimun-eup Jigwang,
Close the door and camp out
Chakgoesacheonbongryeoksa Temple
It's a waste of time
Close the door and camp out
Geumgang Surrender Yokai
It will be good luck
This is
Why aren't you answering the phone?
why?
What do you think Yeomhwa would have done with the Heavenly Earth Fairy?
hey
Sir!
No, why are you angry?
They too
Because my thoughts keep going in that direction
I'm just making random phone calls.
Wait a minute
What can't you hear?
What are you talking about?
Phone sound?
Seongya
Are you here?
To burn my insides today
You made a plan
Why aren't you answering the phone...
Why is your face so scrunchy?
uh?
- mother
- Uh
I'm in an abandoned house
What in an abandoned house?
What happened?
uh?
In an abandoned house there
Uh, tell me
I got caught
Being a shaman
To Gyeonwoo
Byeoksabu, a talisman that chases away ghosts
I can only do it on my face, why...
I'm afraid you won't be able to attain Buddhahood.
I've been by your side for so long
I did it to protect you.
To protect you
If I were a shaman
I think you'll be very hurt
I'm sorry
Because I want to be friends
Just 5 days from tomorrow
Let’s be friends with me for just 5 more days
Because it’s okay to hate and it’s okay to be angry
Let's stay together for 5 more days
To make the guy inside an evil spirit
It's a deliberate barrier
No matter how brave the shaman is
The moment you enter
I'll be a sacrifice
possessed by a demon
You'll lose your life
Oh my?
What does anyone do with evil spirits?
Not a spirit, but a pure living person
Having to get through 100 people
No way...
Is it almost done already?
Are there one or two left?
Did you see the question?
What was it like meeting Yeomhwa in the abandoned house?
- not yet
-Is it a pressure cooker?
Why are you taking so much time?
How did you sleep?
Did you see him yesterday, at the abandoned house?
Hello, I am Yeomhwa, a shaman.
Nice to meet you
Before we talk...
Yes, I saw it.
Did you see it?
What are you doing?
Whatever you say?
Did you touch it?
I didn't say much
We just danced together
Dance?
why?
He asked me to dance the flower lantern dance.
That's a dance that two people do together.
- So...
- Oh my, my.
Are you really a bitch? I am a bitch.
What kind of chlorine is this chlorine? I'm not scared.
Do you dance a custom that is worse than double smoking?
General, general
This guy is going to be such a big mess!
uh? oh!
Uh-huh, what a snout!
why?
It was all people that Mother Wang had called.
He said he came a little earlier than the others.
It's a lie, bright red
Yes?
Don't say anything, boy
An old shaman
What do you do when you have all your arms and legs together?
This damn thing hit the player
Anyone who enters the house
They all used hexes to become sacrifices to evil spirits.
Even risking my life
You know equivalent exchange, right?
What do we have two lives for?
I couldn't go in, I just sealed it from the outside.
A fearless bitch
It's not even a ghost
Why are you trying to manipulate evil spirits?
Isn’t hell scary?
Is hell far away?
Living as a shaman is hell in itself.
Seeing ghosts is not a talent
That place
Build your job properly, very
I'm going to get ready for school
Gyeonwoo, I’m sorry.
Just 5 days
What are the two?
What's going on?
nothing happened
Really?
Yeah
Seeing ghosts is not a talent
That place
Write it
Make up
You two fought
Make up, it's interfering with the performance evaluation.
We didn't fight, we
Do I look like a fool now?
We fought, you guys and it was so loud
For the first time in my life
I really like your speaking style, Hyeri.
What did you say
If you two won't make up
Let's at least find out why we fought, okay?
from morning
I'm dying of frustration, really, ah...
It's personal
It has nothing to do with you
Hey, that's not a straight face.
Soybean bowl
I wish you didn't come to lunch
You are at this moment
Do you want to talk about bean pot?
If it's not this time
When are we going to talk about bean pots?
When a bowl of beans was served at school lunch
I have to talk about the bean pot.
When the bean pot did not appear in the school lunch
If you say you don't like bean soup,
That's gossip
I hate bean bowls twice as much.
I don't hate bean soup that much.
But I feel sorry and say no in front of the bean bowl.
Some people can't speak
I'm afraid that the bean bowl listening will get hurt.
That kind of person quietly
They say they don’t like bean soup
That person is eating a bowl of beans
It's a mistake to think that I hate it twice as much.
0.5 times more likely to dislike it
To protect the soybean rights of the bean bowl
Because I kept my mouth shut
Hey, what are you saying?
What if Park Seong-ah is Bae Gyeon-woo's bean bowl?
Why do I hate bean soup?
Telling me the reason
It's a huge amount of violence.
Um...
I
I'm a shaman
Oh, I said it was a part-time job.
Actually, I'm a shaman
The shaman who said Joo Seung was me.
That's me right
I was blessed when I was 8 years old.
I have been a shaman ever since.
Elementary and middle school students all have to pass the qualification exam.
Even though I was never a student
I've never been a shaman
I wanted to be an ordinary student
So I didn't say anything
I didn't mean to fool you from the beginning, really.
Then I met Gyeonwoo, who absolutely hates shamans.
I wanted to be friends
So
From then on...
I'm sorry
I lied
And I got caught by Gyeonwoo last night.
I have a question
uh
Why did you want to be friends with me?
Ah...
That's...
If you want to be friends
Just be friends
Is there any reason for that?
Even so, shamans usually
I really hate it so much
Just say it?
Not just friends
I'm protecting you for three or seven days.
They're not just friends, they're there for a reason, right?
Lady, that's right, but
You are destined to die in 37 days
That sound
You have to tell me after protecting that person.
What to do before that
It's scaring and threatening.
Oh, that's true too
How many days are left?
5 days
Oh, that much?
Even I can't find the flame
How do you find the general?
Did you just fall off your shoe?
You won't find it anyway
Why bother buying it?
Don't open your mouth
I said I would take care of my troubles.
Even if I turn on the emergency contact network?
chloride he
Did you prepare very well?
Selling my house and my office
Cancel all reservations
I scraped together all the money I had in hand.
He even hung up his cell phone and went diving.
I guess there's still something scary left
Get out of the way, if you see something hidden,
What's left that's scary, that?
So as not to be disturbed by anything
I cut it all off
once evil spirit
I'm trying to get it right, now.
Then I have to find more
find
I need to completely rip that guy out of his mind.
Going
Anyway, the shamans who received the spirit of General
It's all like me
That guy’s soldier mentality that cracks open ramen
Don't tell me if you've been in the military
I was the only one who went to the military!
Didn’t you discharge your military service?
You got excited when you were in the military, suddenly!
The unit is at attention, but...
Until today, unconditionally
I'm going to make a PPT
No one can go home before then
and you two
Now it's archery and all.
I won't look at that.
Okay?
let's go
First of all, I will never get caught.
I knew you were a shaman
you and me
If you know that we were in the same group from the beginning
That bastard, he really has nowhere to lean on.
Yeah
I'll even apologize to you
Stop being sorry and take care of yourself
Keep it and be sure to receive an apology after three or seven days.
Got it?
Ugh, when are they going to make PPT again? Ugh.
something on my leg
Is there anything I need to see?
Oh, it's nothing
let's go
You're sleeping well
my baby
we don't have a baby
Baby, no baby
Oh my, it’s dirty!
- Oh my, it's dirty!
- No baby!
Wow, stop looking through the trash!
New girl! baby is not here
Baby shouldn't be in a place like this
- I'm in big trouble, really.
- No baby.
Oh my, it’s dirty, really.
What's wrong? huh?
- what's the matter?
- I...
My new wife, oh my!
You thief!
Won't you give me my baby?
What's wrong, wait a minute!
Ah, Doyeon!
No, why are you doing that!
You thief!
Come out and see!
Calm down, calm down
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Wow!
You both can't stop!
Don't look, don't look
If it's noisy, the baby will wake up.
baby spirit
It's not all harmful
What more can a baby do than cry?
What if you cry? Just appease it
But what if I couldn’t console him?
From then on it's a disaster
Huh?
No, no, don't cry.
I'm not a bad person
Just a person with bad luck, eh
Peekaboo! Orololo
Peekaboo!
Ah... thank you
I don't know, just a human talisman.
Why is it broken?
Did you do skinship?
Are you hurt?
Where are you looking?
It's no big deal
- Hey, you're bleeding.
- Oh, it's okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Are you okay?
Boy, I got a little scratched.
I think ‘ho’ will suffice.
Are you hurt?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
It's okay
Are you hurt?
Uh, it's okay
What is it? Why did the cup suddenly break?
- I don't know, for now...
- I'm going home.
Hey, you are at this moment
Do you want to have a quick chat at home?
Are you saying you're going home when you're done?
I'm done
Wow, PPT is
Doyeon handled it safely?
something is strange
I need to find out more
You want to go to my house?
- why?
- Uh...
I thought it would be nice to just become friends
Why is that good?
I just fell in love with my PPT skills.
If you just want to learn a trick, I don’t know.
Uh, I want to learn.
Uh, ah...
hello
No one, dual income
Aha
Uh, wow, wow, wow...
amazing
What's so great about it?
Would you like to hear more details?
Ah, uh, uh, there's that.
Well, that...
Ah...
Weren’t you possessed by Doyeon?
You have great insight, right?
It's easy to talk like this
No way
Is 50 too small?
Then
1 million won?
Patricia is my child
Do you think you will give in to capital like that?
I'll treat that kid like my own.
I will cherish and love you
It's because I fell in love at first sight
How... not possible?
Uh, huh?
You're lying.
The love that pours money into me as soon as I see it
It can't be true love
go
I'm his mom, you don't deserve it
Ah...
Uh, okay, I'll go.
I'll go first
Calm down, uh
Just 5 days from tomorrow
Let’s be friends with me for just 5 more days
What on earth are you planning?
Hey Gyeonwoo
Hey, Bae Gyeon-woo!
Let's high five!
Are you a virgin?
It's friendship
It was all witchcraft
Not sympathy, not friendship.
You were just a shaman from the beginning
What happens
Doesn't it look like there's nothing on your face?
Do you want to use a talisman?
amulet
The human talisman didn't work.
The baby spirit attached to the doll must be very strong.
I need to get that doll
I would have taken some time to lose strength.
Being a shaman
Didn't you get eaten by the boy who got caught?
- Yes
- Then you don’t know.
Is the baby spirit strong or are you weak?
Whether it's a human talisman or a nabal
All talismans are the same, boy
When did the talisman fall off?
think about it carefully
When does it fall?
I don't know, it's me
Have you never fallen?
how
Would you like to write one?
Let's live moistly
Now, society...
Oh, I'm annoyed, this headache
Teacher
Oh, my head hurts.
Oh, I see, why are you like this?
Hey guys, open the window.
Let's get some air, quickly.
Teacher, uh... please go to the nurse's office.
Oh, yeah, go quickly.
Come on, let's do some stretching, sleep loudly.
Doyeonah
Hey, have you ever thought about it?
What are you thinking?
That, over there, that doll.
After all, can’t you give it to me?
under! Hey, Goo Do-yeon
Why are you suddenly spraying water?
Are you a sociopath?
I don't think that's what you want to say
What?
Oh, guys, don't fight.
I'm really okay
you stay still
if you don't mind
Well, should I be okay too?
Don’t you do performance evaluations?
You're doing it
This is the library, so lower your volume.
Lower your voice, you're louder
And the second page
You got this wrong, do it again
No matter how loud I am
Will it be louder than you, and
The page...
I can't keep up with you because you don't have much insight.
What, discernment?
Oh, I think he's going to cry, that guy.
Uh, first of all...
Whether it works or not
Human talisman, just one more time
please
just one more time
Witchcraft?
also?
uh?
Even though I don’t know you
Do you know anything about shamans?
To me so far
You were still using witchcraft, right?
Is it okay if I treat you like this?
How did you know?
How hell is your heart right now?
The effect of a human talisman
completely disappeared
I
Now I can't protect Gyeonwoo
Whether it's a human talisman or a nabal
All talismans are the same, boy
think about it carefully
When did the talisman fall off?
Why are you here? I'm not lying down
It's okay, it didn't hurt much.
Doesn't it hurt your heart to be here?
It's all self-employed, right?
Why so much
Can you lend me something?
Reliably?
That's enough
Huh?
Oh my, Gyeonwoo
Oh my, this, oh my, this...
Oh my, Gyeonwoo...
The effect of the human talisman has disappeared.
Skinship doesn't work anymore
Oh, then the bookshelf fell over?
Yeah, it's bad luck
Why is that just disappearing now?
Because Gyeonwoo hates me
A person who hates
No matter how nice you are to me, I don’t like it.
It's no use
It's a similar principle
Why do you keep saying things like that?
I should have stopped when I got caught.
I should have found another way quickly
I guess I was greedy without realizing it
I'm doing this for Gyeonwoo.
So it can't be helped
Actually, it's all just an excuse
There's no way I'm the only way
To save people
Is there any such thing as the only way?
That's just what I wanted to do
Even for a moment...
I wanted to be someone important to Gyeonwoo.
So what are you going to do from now on?
I'll find another way as soon as possible
Uh, for now
I prepared just in case.
Now this is the only way to prepare
ok
I'll put it in your panties
I came to my senses
cater to my greed
You almost missed Gyeonwoo.
Now I won’t be so clumsy in asking for friends.
As a fairy of heaven and earth
I will only focus on saving Gyeonwoo.
Yes, if you feel dizzy
I think you can leave the hospital right away.
Oh my, thank you for your hard work
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Yes
- thank you
let's go
I'll take you to the bar
Yes, our good body friend
Please take care of him.
I'll calculate the hospital bill and go.
Oh, no, sir, you don’t have to...
Stay still, man.
It's my heart
If you refuse, you'll die, really.
just say thank you
Adults usually have a lot of money
Ah...
Yeah
It came out to 498,000 won.
Huh?
It's 498,000 won.
It's okay, it's okay
Oh, it's okay, let's go now.
40...
I'm preparing the amulet for now.
100 as soon as possible
The real problem is the baby spirit.
Oh my, come quickly
Fairy, please get the ghost out of here.
Oh my, new wife
You can't bring this in here, okay?
uh? no
No, no, no
It's mine! wait for a sec!
I lost my baby in the last month of pregnancy.
Ugh, too bad, whatever.
After that, I lost my mind
I walk around with a stroller like that all day.
Recently, I picked up a doll.
Did you carry it around like a baby?
Ah, I guess I wrote something right then.
No, he threw away the doll somewhere.
I'm going to find it
Search through all the trash in the neighborhood.
Oh my gosh
Look at me smiling
That's just crazy, huh?
- It's not possession.
- Huh?
Take me to the hospital
No, I didn't even look closely.
It's a shaman, can't you tell just by looking at it?
Have you lost your mind or are you possessed by a ghost?
Ah, I lost my mind.
Maybe he's possessed by a ghost
There is no
People who are sober are not possessed by ghosts.
Why?
I've already lost my mind
How can a ghost be possessed?
I don't have the brains to be possessed
On the contrary, the ghost side is very anxious.
What is this?
What the hell is me
I wonder if I'm not scared like this
Give me my baby!
baby mom
Baby mama!
What does the baby look like?
baby?
-Pretty
- You're wearing a blue dress, right?
White blouse inside
As for the size, uh...
Are you being a bit annoying at this level?
The blue skirt is shiny
There are too many holes in the clothes above
I held the baby tightly because I was afraid he might be cold.
That's him
I can do it, I can get rid of it baby spirit
No...
fairy, fairy
Who are you?
Oh, hello?
I'm Doyeon's friend.
I don't have any friends?
It's me, Park Seong-ah
Cosplay?
Oh, you're a shaman
Ah!
Boy, I got this, this
Write it
Yes, hello, this is Gyeonwoo Phone.
Hey
What are you doing with someone else’s cell phone?
Hey, this
That's not what I wanted
Just what happened...
Must be a foreigner
My name is English, H
Hey... is this an important call?
Hey, sorry
Are you saying Patricia is a ghost?
You feel like you're choking and throwing up these days.
Will your head break?
It's all because of the baby spirit attached there.
The reason is weak?
You'll have nightmares
A nightmare where a baby cries all night long
When I said I would give you 1 million won
It would have been better if you had just given it to me
You're saying extremely villainous things.
Suddenly like this
Why did you reveal your true colors?
Baby spirits are naturally difficult to transfer to the capital.
Because we can't communicate
Soothe me not to cry
Just putting him to sleep is a success.
The person who is best at it
'Cause I just found it
Who is it?
mom
It's Heena
more than you want
I'll be much more unhappy
don't worry
Nothing good happens to me
you know
Don't cry
Pull yourself together well
I'm sorry, I...
I again...
What is he?
I didn't mean to listen
I just heard it
Why are you calling me crying?
Unhappy?
Why are you answering that phone call?
Hey, what?
Hey friend
He was a good kid
I made it like this
So you guys should do the same.
That's okay
Keep your distance from a guy like me
What, what?
Hey Jiho
It's really okay
I won't blame you
Is he crazy, really?
What if I don’t give it to you?
Can’t you see that I came here like this?
I'll take it from you
If you leave it as is, you will continue to hurt.
Suffering from insomnia and chronic headaches
But it doesn't kill me
But some kids are different
die
Bad luck that will end in a headache for you
It came to him as an accident.
There are a lot of dolls
Give up at least one thing for a friend
i don't have any friends
Do it now, then
me and friend
Unlike usual, you are very reckless.
I understand why the woodcutter took the fairy’s clothes.
So badly...
You're getting stronger...
praise thanks
What it looks like at school
Is it all a lie?
maybe
Patricia got it used.
My mom said she looked upset
I secretly threw it away
I guess that lady picked it up
Then I discovered it by chance
I brought you back
Even though it hurt this much
What do you like about staying in this world?
Are you coming now?
what?
Why are you here? Are you waiting for me?
uh
Why? What happened to Gyeonwoo?
Write it
What's going to happen from now on
I'll do it
human talisman
Why do you do that to Gyeonwoo?
To be honest, I didn’t fully understand it, did I?
more than you hope for
I'll be even more unhappy
But when I was next to you, I understood.
I end up doing that too.
If that kid dies like this
I feel like I can't live because I'm so unfair
Is it a human talisman or something?
I can do it too, right?
Uh...
You can't do it?
I can do it
If you feel that way
In this world, there is no one on your side
not a single person
For the poor, obnoxious bastard
you are a shaman
I am a talisman
For now it's just like that
Something with eyes, nose, and mouth
Among the things you used a lot of hands on
Give the one with eyes, nose, and mouth to Gyeonhero.
When Gyeonwoo is alone without you
He will protect Gyeonwoo for you.
Come out, eyes, nose, mouth...
Hey
Why are you...
It has eyes, nose, and mouth!
Treat me with respect, I cherish you
I don't need it?
Take it, man!
Honestly, I couldn't evaluate my performance.
Let's do it together, all day today
I'm busy today
Why? You're busy with me
Should I get angry?
Contact me when you're done with busy work.
I'm waiting
Hey, take this.
Treat it with respect, cherish it.
Is it a leech?
Let's go find mom
Are you pushing a stroller?
Have you seen the woman wearing a floral dress?
Ah...
Nope
Oh, what a surprise.
Where are you?
No baby!
No baby...
Someone I don't know
I'm crying alone on the side of the road
Still
I wish I could go next to that person and comfort him.
The kid I like
Just stand there
Until the tears stop
You can do the standing thing, right?
I don't know why I'm crying
Did you all cry?
You can't touch something like this.
It's support
support
let's go
hello
The stroller is so pretty
baby car
Baby car, isn’t it pretty?
Oh yes
Huh? What is that?
- huh?
- What is that?
Oh my
The baby is so pretty too
we don't have a baby
Baby!
Uh, where have you been?
Mom kept looking for me
Ah, pretty
I know why you didn't leave
You found your real mom
It's so amazing
Everything about these two is fake
That love alone is real
goodbye
No...
Hey Gyeonwoo
Even if I'm not your friend
Even if it's a lie
Even if it's fake
If it hurts like this here
Isn't this one thing real?
It hurts so much
I really...
I think I'm going to die
Is there a reason why your guts got better?
I don't know, you
Why are you so nice to me?
Why don't we stop here?
He will have to live a long time too
Because when I die, I'm going to hell
Ah, why do I feel so low?
Do you think I am a fool?
You're doing it because Seong-ah told you to do it.
If you are weak, you will be defeated, originally.
No way?
No, that's not...
Is it true what Seong-ah said?
Just hate me